

About me

As a highly motivated and committed web developer and graduate Engineer for Electrical Engineering and Telecommunication, you will get with me:

- Work experience in various technical fields
- Compliance with high quality standards
- On-time project delivery
- IT-driven curiosity

Out of passion for digital technology and trends, I switched my career path to programming in 2019. In order to generate more know-how, I successfully completed a full-stack Web development course based on the MERN stack at DCI. I look forward to providing you with my knowledge and analytical skills in Web development.

Skills

Technologies: JavaScript Frameworks:

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Node.js
- React Native
- React Redux
- Angular
- Vue
- jQuery
- Bootstrap

Databases:

Version Control:

- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- MySQL
- Git GitHub
- GitLab

Languages

English (C1) German (B2) Serbian

Contact

Croatian

• Frankfurt am Main

+49 174 623 15 25

☑ alen.eftimov@gmail.com

https://github.com/Alen-Eftimov

in www.linkedin.com/in/eftimov-alen

https://www.xing.com/profile /Alen_Eftimov3/cv

Alen Eftimov

Full Stack Web Developer

Education

2019 - 2021

DCI Hamburg - DigitalCareerInstitute gGmbH

Full Stack Web Developer

Successful completion of a one-year training course based on MERN Stack, including several practical project works

1995 - 2006

Faculty of Electronic Engineering Niš - University of Niš, Serbia M.Sc. in Electrical and Telecommunications Engineering

Experience

11/2021 06/2022 Site-Works - Frankfurt am Main

Web Developer:

- On the satisfaction clients I updated websites such as Clean FFM, Sander Group, T21, Gerbermühle, 1250Nieder Eschbach... with the following technologies Java Script, HTML, CSS, CMS (Grav, WordPress, Contao), GitHub, GitLab.
- I worked on the development of a mobile application for providing Taxi services. I used React Native and Android Studio technology.

2014 - 2017

Independent Designer Engineer of Telecommunications systems -Belgrade, Serbia

- Designing: Video surveillance, Alarm systems, Fire alarms, Sound systems, Computer, Telephone and Optical networks.
- Technologies used: AutoCad, MS Office

2013 - 2014 CEG International - Doha, Qatar

Supervisor / Consultant for Telecommunications systems:

Supervision - Work on Telecommunications systems projects.

2007 - 2013

ARHIPRO - Belgrade, Serbia

Designer Engineer for Telecommunications systems:

Work on Telecommunications systems projects.

Relevant Projects

Dr.House - https://dr-house.herokuapp.com

- Multi-purpose health care website for hospitals, clinics, doctors and patients with a focus on CRUD admin page.
- Technologies used: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, EJS, Bootstrap, MongoDB

WebShopReactApp - https://web-shop-app-react.netlify.app

- Frontend eCommerce application based on React.
- Technologies used: React, React Hooks, React Router, ES6, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Material UI.
- portfolioAlen https://alen-eftimov-portfolio.herokuapp.com

Expertise

Web development Responsive design

Clean Coding

Database systems

Hobbies & Interests

